(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T23:18:17.332319",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Notice for Visitors]
事前登録受付中！
[Pre-registration Now Open!]
ローソンへお越しの皆さん
To everyone visiting Lawson,
2025年12月
[December 2025]
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Lawson Campaign Confirmed!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
[These 6 members will appear!]
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
[Details scheduled to be released March 9 (Mon)!]
バンダイブースを出展！
Bandai booth exhibition!
注目の新商品も初公開！
Featured new products revealed for the first time!
会場限定！オリジナルフォトブース！
Venue exclusive! Original photo booth!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get limited-edition cards at the booth!
来場してね！
Be sure to visit!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now!
さあ 乗り込もう！
Come on, let's jump aboard!
Ridin' on Dreams
Yeah！
Yeah!
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey！(Hey！) Hey！(Hey！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
Yeah！
Yeah!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream,
想像できないような
it turned into feelings so vast
想いになったんだ
they were beyond imagination.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lose our way,
絆が船になる
our bonds become a ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even the smallest anxieties,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can just blow them all away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey,
漕いでる途中に
as we row forward right now,
困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships too.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, this can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves
“らしく”輝いていたい
and keep shining in our own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
is a treasure to us,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so let's hold hands and call out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！
and keep going further!
Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey！(Hey！) Hey！(Hey！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
Yeah！
Yeah!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds
行く先乱そうとも
try to disrupt our path ahead,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
that our resolve would never waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
A back that says, "I have to do this right!"
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing can be taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
struggling not knowing where to begin,
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
little by little, we formed a circle and found
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Embracing even our incompleteness,
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
わずかな希望でも
Even with just a tiny sliver of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always,
馬鹿にされても
even if people laugh at us,
信じたい！
keep believing!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, these feelings are overflowing!
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, this can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves
“らしく”輝いていたい
and keep shining in our own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
is a treasure to us,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so let's hold hands and call out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行けるから！
because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Standing back up time and time again,
笑顔でいたい
we want to share smiles together.
願いだって みんなで、さあ！
Our wishes too, everyone together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Connecting hands, exceeding all imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey！(Hey！) Hey！(Hey！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
Yeah！
Yeah!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！ Ridin' on dreams
Come on, let's hop on! Ridin' on dreams
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream
想像できないような
into something unimaginable,
想いになったんだ
it became a feeling like this.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕らは
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it away.
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
as we row, there will surely be hardships too.
それを力に変えて
Turning that into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
we'll move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしさ”輝いていたい
We want to shine as ourselves
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure to me
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world without a map
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep on going!
Ridin' on dreams
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our destination,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve will not waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
"I've got to do this right!" That push
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship
どっから始業したらいいかもがいて
struggling, wondering where to even begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
little by little, coming together, we found
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream.
未完成も愛して
Loving even our incompleteness
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are as one
わずかな希望でも
Even with a sliver of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will forever...
馬鹿にされても
Even if people make fun of us,
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしさ”輝いていたい
We want to shine as ourselves
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure to me
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world without a map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Rising up time and time again,
笑顔で合い言葉
smiling with our shared password
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
With everyone's wishes, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Hand in hand, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep on going!
Ridin' on dreams
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！ Ridin' on dreams
Come on, let's hop on! Ridin' on dreams
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream
想像できないような
into something unimaginable,
想いになったんだ
it became a feeling like this.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕らは
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it away.
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over again.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop on!
Ridin' on dreams
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream,
想像できないような 想いになったんだ
it turned into feelings beyond imagination.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら 絆が船になる
No matter how lost we get, our bonds become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ 吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
Even a little bit of anxiety gets blown away.
果てない旅路を今 漕いでる途中に
On our endless journey, as we row along,
困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships too.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining in my own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, it's my precious treasure.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to one another,
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
Ridin' on dreams
急な風が僕らの 行く先乱そうとも
Even if sudden winds try to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだ 覚悟は揺るがない
we swore on that day; our resolve won't waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中 明日への橋になる
"I must do this right!" That drive becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね “あたりまえ”は無いから
We must treasure it even more, because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that begins from a small ship.
どっから始めているか もがいて
Struggling with where to even begin,
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
bit by bit, gathered in a circle, we found
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 未完成も愛して
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, loving even our incompleteness,
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 想いは一つだ
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, our feelings are as one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh わずかな希望でも
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, even with just a sliver of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I, forever,
馬鹿にされても
even if they make fun of us,
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining in my own way.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, it's my precious treasure.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to one another,
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Standing up again and again,
笑顔でいたい
we want to keep smiling together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Let's make our wish together, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
Ridin' on dreams
We're ready to greet the world! We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start, let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, cheerfully meeting heart to heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream, I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been, with vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop; straight to the top, that's right!
We're ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine! Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves, we're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new stage, let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing no matter where we are, no matter how far, we can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly, playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see, making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen, all we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere! Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way, with each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls— let's make friends, making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans,
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion—
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere! Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way, with each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls— let's make friends, making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we'll connect the world!
Connecting all of the world!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉が
Words layered in harmony
届いて
reach out...
Yeah!
あなたらしく描いては
Painting as you truly are,
落ちないと笑ってた
laughing that you wouldn't fall.
ブレないよ
I won't falter,
あの日の続きを見よう
let's see the continuation of that day.
遠慮しないで
Don't hold back,
汗も着こなして
wear even your sweat with pride,
扉を叩いて
knock on the door,
連れて行くよ
and I'll take you along.
どんなこともきっと
Whatever happens, surely
一緒なら叶えていける
if we're together, we can make it come true.
鳴りやまない 希望のベル ほら
Listen to the unrelenting bells of hope!
聞こえてる
I can hear it,
響いてる
it's echoing...
さあ！
Come on!
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Words layered in harmony,
鮮やかな日々の向こう
beyond those vibrant days,
ずっと君と
forever with you,
広がるよ
expanding wide.
重なり ハートに
Coming together in our hearts,
結んだ夢が
the tied dreams
空へかけてゆく
soar into the sky.
きらめき乗せて
Carrying brilliance,
あなたへ
to you...
届けて
reach out!
メロディ どこまでも
Melody, wherever you go!
何気ないことを思い出す
Remembering the ordinary moments...
じゃないよで深呼吸
Take a deep breath instead
みたいで楽しいな 魔法の言葉
It's fun, like a magic word
ふっと息ついて ふっと振り返って また君を押して
Taking a breath, looking back, and pushing you forward again
その度にちょっと勇気出して 明日へ飛び込んでいけ
Each time, gather a little courage and jump into tomorrow
La La La La 降り積もる道しるべはまだ
La la la la, the accumulated signposts are still...
La La La La 覚えてる 聞こえてる 歌
La la la la, I remember, I hear the song
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら 足跡に虹がかかる
Harmony, when I reach out my hand, a rainbow forms over our footsteps
きっと晴れる 映し出すステージ
It will surely clear up, illuminating the stage
ハートに記した場所へ
To the place marked in our hearts
運ぶ約束を 輝きに乗せて 世界へ
Carrying our promise, riding on the shine, out to the world
響けメロディー いつまでも
Resonate, melody, forevermore
君と踏み出したあの第一歩 あの瞬間が
That first step I took with you, that very moment
宝物だって胸を張る 今
I proudly hold it as a treasure now
歩いて 話して はしゃいで 笑顔で行こうな
Walking, talking, having fun, let's go with smiles
色褪せないまま
Remaining unfaded
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Blending together, our voices, look
聞こえてる 歌
I hear the song
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな日々の向こう
Harmony, our stacked words, beyond those vivid days
ずっと君と 広がるストーリー
Forever with you, an unfolding story
ハートに結んだ夢が 空へ駆け抜けてゆく
The dreams bound in our hearts race up into the sky
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
Riding on the sparkle, to you
世界へ
To the world
響けメロディー どこまでも
Resonate, melody, everywhere
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's shining!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal
パレ パレ パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, we go searching
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as it takes
ひとりごとつぶやいた
I muttered a monologue to myself
ただ 始まりたくて走った
Just wanting to begin, I ran
遠く 暗闇に灯った
Far away, lit up in the darkness
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name far too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思いで
That was a memory far too kind
もっと 近づけたくて手を伸ばした
Wanting to get closer, I reached out my hand
思いがけず 結び合った
Unexpectedly, we connected
ほら 今 迷子はいなくなった
Look, now there are no lost children anymore
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's shining!
悔しさも愛しさも 全ておいで
Regrets and affection, come bring them all
風 夢 羽ばたいて飛べるさ
Wind, dreams, flutter your wings and you can fly
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
A modest prayer is light, a sign of no end
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
これから これから 広がる パレ パレ
From now on, spreading far and wide, parade, parade!
まだ 頼りない予感の
Of an uncertain premonition still
歌を 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Singing this song isn't embarrassing at all
誰も 解けないおまじない
A spell that no one can undo
いつか また会えるおまじない
A spell to meet again someday
あの第一歩 始まったストーリー
That first step, the story that began
数え切れない言の葉
Untold words beyond count,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
are not feelings that can be counted.
ほら 今 僕らを 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one.
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's so beautiful.
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
Moments of mutual forgiveness make the night shine.
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, shine, kaleidoscope, a one-of-a-kind sky.
相応しい旅路とは 君と在ることさ
A worthy journey means being with you.
君と在ることなんだ
It's all about being with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば 「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
When I hear "I'm back," I'll shout "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
暗がりを満たすのは
What fills up the darkness...
君だ 僕だ！
...is you, is me!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both regret and affection.
風、夢、羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
Modest prayers become light, a sign of no end.
君と 飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, what a wonderful start!
ここから これから
From here, from now on.
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
せーの、せーの、ステージ3、行くよー！
One two, one two, Stage 3, let's go!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
あの太陽よりもっと高く 手を伸ばして
Reach your hand out higher than that sun!
長伸ばした 季節色の影の上を
Walking over long-stretched, season-colored shadows,
爽やか 足跡で飾って
decorating them with refreshing footsteps.
ワクワクする公園に向かおうか
Shall we head to the exciting park?
決められた未来と
Opposite of a predetermined future,
逆の風景ばっか行こうとしてる
I'm trying to go toward contrasting scenery.
間違ってないか
Am I making a mistake?
がっかりしないか
Will I be disappointed?
散々迷って また今日に立っていた
After wandering so much, I stood here again today.
誰も歩かない 道の先で
Ahead on a path nobody walks,
かすんだ声がする
a hazy voice echoes.
誰も気づけない
Nobody can notice it,
予想外な明日が今 ひらめいちゃったんだ
an unexpected tomorrow just flashed into my mind.
どうしよう まだまだ音を重ねていく
What should I do? Stacking sound upon sound even more.
みんなが変わってるって笑った毎日が
The days everyone laughed, saying I was weird,
突然特別になったから
suddenly became special.
今この世界に問いに行こう
Now let's go question this world.
まっすぐ登ったまま消えない太陽に 手を伸ばして
Reach your hand out to the sun that stays climbed up straight without fading!
覚えてるんだ 初めは隠してた癖も
I remember even the habits I hid at first,
恥ずかしくて 語れない夢も
and the dreams too embarrassing to talk about.
一つ一つは 特別に見えなくても
Even if each one doesn't seem special on its own,
重なり合って ほら 今色めいた
look, they overlap and colorfully bloom now!
まつりす！
Matsuris!
まつりに今会えて、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to see Matsuri today!
この後は、まつりの格好いい歌です！
Next up is a cool song from Matsuri!
これからも、まつりはまつりらしく、突き進んでいくよ！
From here on, Matsuri will keep charging forward in true Matsuri style!
まつりも君の居場所でいたいから！
Because I want to be your place to belong, too!
大好きなのー！
I love you so much!
間違ってないよ
You're not wrong,
がっかりしないよ
you won't be disappointed!
散々な道が一番楽しいんだ
The roughest path is the most fun of all!
なんだろう ちょっとだけ頭がズレていく
What is this? My mind is slipping just a bit...
みんなと違ってるって凹んだ毎日が
Those days I felt down for being different from everyone...
きっと最高になるから
...are sure to become the best! So...
今から世界をひっくり返しに行こう
Let's go flip the world upside down right now!
すっかり登ったまま消えない太陽
The sun that's fully risen and won't disappear...
おい タオルぶん回そう！
Hey, swing your towels around!
まだまだ音を動かしていく
Keep moving to the sound more and more!
みんなと変わってるって笑った毎日が
Those days we laughed at being different from everyone...
突然とっぴもないから
...came so suddenly out of nowhere, so...
今すぐ世界に恋しに行こう
Let me go fall in love with the world right now!
あの空の眩しさに負けないくらいに
So as not to lose to the glare of that sky,
手を伸ばして
reach out your hands!
Everybody put your hands up!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Say things I never wanted to say
Up in arms, who can I please? You?
Livin' day by day
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Rinse and repeat until it's Sunday
Hold it, so frustrated
Ya know, I can't do it no more
I'll say
No good, down to the core
Hear you knockin', beatin' down my door!
Yell out, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
No, I'm never, never gonna-
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Hey, hey!
I'll stop me
I'll never figure it out
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
You want me to know what I just don't know
Mold me into her? Into him? No
Little did you know, I'm just me, let it go
Lock me inside a pin of your perfection, correction
Tearin' me down
Am I what you like now?
Now don't tell me what, what to do, what to say, what to think
About everything, but did you ever think?
I'll say
Good with bein' so bad
What's the issue? I'll screw up again!
Yell out, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
No, I'm never, never gonna-
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Comfortable and pathetic
I like it that way, get it?
You're brutal, judgemental
It's never that simple, but I still want
To meet your harsh criteria
Too bad I'm never gonna
I'm never gonna fit
Hell yeah!
One, two, three, go!
Yell out, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
No, I'm never, never gonna-
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Hey, hey!
I'll stop me
I'll never figure it out
Never, never, never let go...
こんまっするー！ 白銀ノエルです！
Kon-muscle! I'm Shirogane Noel!
みんなー！ 盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone! Let's get hyped up!
終わらない 終わらない
It never ends, it never ends
仕事山積み 終わらない
The pile of work never ends
止まらない 止まらない
It doesn't stop, it doesn't stop
それでも時間は 止まらない
Even so, time doesn't stop
ヘットヘト
Completely exhausted
たまり溜まったヘト
Accumulated exhaustion
テンパっと 打ち返すバット
Panicking, swinging the bat back
本気で魅せる 金属バット
Showing off for real with a metal bat
今日も手配 今日も手配
Preparing again today, preparing again today
脳もアムージ
My brain is amusing
Gimme Gimme Juicy
細延体 細延体
Slender body, slender body
ため息プレスで MPスカスカ？
MP empty from sigh press?
自分自身に 厳しすぎちゃう
Being way too hard on yourself
ドジっ子 ヘラヘラ 優等生
Clumsy girl, laughing it off, model student
さっぱり足りない 順応性
Completely lacking adaptability
自分自身と 真剣に向き合う
Seriously facing yourself
一番 必要なものは
What is needed most of all...
トレビアン！
Très bien!
ご褒美 頂戴
Give me a reward
てんてこ舞うような リズムに バイバイしちゃえ
Say bye-bye to a chaotic rhythm
ドレミファ
Do-Re-Mi-Fa
ノートに ご来校
Welcome to the note
ギュッギュッと 詰めちゃダメ もう一回！
Don't pack it tightly, one more time!
トレビアン！
Très bien!
ご褒美 頂戴
Give me a reward
てんてこ舞うような リズムに バイバイしちゃえ
Say bye-bye to a chaotic rhythm
ドレミファ
Do-Re-Mi-Fa
ノートに ご来校
Welcome to the note
ギュッギュッと 詰めちゃダメ
Don't pack it tightly
どんどん クリーンダウン
Cleaning down more and more
ギュッギュッと 詰めたご褒美 どんどん好きになる
A tightly packed reward, I'll like it more and more
ぎゅー！ どん！ ぎゅー！ どん！ どん！
Gyu! Don! Gyu! Don! Don!
ぎゅー！ どん！ ぎゅっとして どーん！
Gyu! Don! Hug me tight and BAM!
さあさ ぎゅうどんだ ぎゅうどんだ
Come on, it's beef bowl time, beef bowl time
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together
黄身となかよく かーにばる
A carnival getting along with the egg yolk
とろとろ ちゅわわー
Melty and squishy~
ほろり お肉 お肉
Tender beef, beef
つまんじゃダメ
Don't snatch it
全部食べたら ほめちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you
なでなで よしよし ちゅっちゅっちゅー
Pat pat, good boy, kiss kiss kiss
あびゃー！ あびゃー！ あびゃびゃー！
Abya~! Abya~! Abyabya~!
あびゃびゃ！ あびゃびゃ！ あびゃー！
Abyabya! Abyabya! Abya~!
あびゃびゃ！ あびゃびゃ！ あびゃびゃ！
Abyabya! Abyabya! Abyabya!
あびゃー！ あびゃびゃー！
Abya~! Abyabya~!
洗脳開始！
Brainwashing begin!
すっきー！ すきすき だいちゅっきー！
Love you~! Love love, love you so much~!
らっびゅー！ らびゅらびゅ 洗脳中〜
Love you~! Love you love you, currently brainwashing~
むっちー！ むちむち 責めちゃダメ〜
Plump~! Plump and squishy, don't blame me~
よく出来ました！ ほっぺにちゅー！
Well done! Kiss on the cheek~!
ところが 全然足りません
But it's not enough at all
それでも 全然足りません
Even so, it's not enough at all
まだまだ 全然足りないの
Still, still, it's not enough at all
ドキがムネムネ 止まらな〜い
My heart won't stop pounding~
牛丼を食べるときは
When you eat a beef bowl,
お口でふーふーってして…って
blow on it with your mouth... wait,
あっ、いきなりがっついちゃって かわいい〜
Ah, digging right in, so cute~
優しく… 丁寧に、だぞ？
Gently... politely, got it?
あははっ… いい子いい子。
Ahaha... good child, good child.
…お腹、いっぱいになっちゃったね。
...Your tummy got full, didn't it?
…一緒に、寝ちゃう？
...Shall we go to sleep together?
おやすみなさーい♪
Good night~♪
もしも キミが シュンとしちゃっても
Even if you feel down,
ぎゅーって ぎゅーって ぎゅーって！ 抱きしめてあげる
Hugging tight, tight, tight! I'll embrace you
行くよー！ 幕張ー！
Here we go! Makuhari~!
さあさ ぎゅうどんだ ぎゅうどんだ
Come on, it's beef bowl time, beef bowl time
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together
キミと何度でも かーにばる
A carnival with you time and time again
とろとろ ちゅわわー
Melty and squishy~
ほろり お肉 お肉
Tender beef, beef
つまんじゃダメ
Don't snatch it
全部食べたら ほめちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you
なでなで よしよし ちゅっちゅっちゅー
Pat pat, good boy, kiss kiss kiss
あびゃー！
Abya~!
せーのっ！ ぎゅうどんだーん！
Ready, set, go! Beef bowl BAM!
大好き！
I love you!
ぎゅっとして どーん！ まだまだ どーん！
Hug me tight and BAM! Still more, BAM!
みんなとノエルの ぎゅうどんだーん！
Everyone and Noel's beef bowl BAM!
ぎゅーーーっ！
Gyuuuu!
ありがとー！
Thank you~!
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
lock on
目と目が合えば I know
When our eyes meet, I know
キミこそが相棒
You're my true partner
メロつかせる才能
A talent to make you fall head over heels
(make it? break it? make it? break it?)
パッと見 天使でも (でも)
At a glance, an angel (even so)
中には潜む デーモン (デーモン)
A demon lurks inside (a demon)
So ギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
So with contrast and charm, we're invincible
Hater はシカト
Ignore the haters
「へー、あっそ！」
"Oh, is that so?"
一蓮托生 オーガナイズ
In it together, organized
退屈に用は無い
No room for boredom
一線画すよ ボーダーライン
Drawing a clear line, a border
届かない？ しょーがない
Can't reach us? Too bad
ウチらが集えば バリ baddest (baddest)
When we assemble, we're the absolute baddest
見惚れちゃうでしょ？
You can't take your eyes off us, right?
Look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない 絶対
Never leaving you behind, ever
ついてきて 5MC's
Follow us, the 5 MCs
本気の フライデーナイト
Our Friday night in full swing
make it? break it?
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Stay true to myself, wild and bold
夢に強引 going, going on!
Forcing our way to our dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜いて行け
Blast straight through the middle
Can't get enough
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
有象無象 沸かす FLOW GLOW
FLOW GLOW hype up the crowd
Ay 口先より行動
Ay, actions speak louder than words
If you wanna be マイメン
If you wanna be my main
よそ見とか ナシで
No looking away
Warning! 没頭 ほら 没頭 ほら
Warning! Get immersed, look, get immersed
味わっちゃって
Savor every moment
Burning! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Burning! Get hotter, get hotter
ハイになっちゃって
Get high on the vibe
置いてかない 絶対
Never leaving you behind, ever
ついてきて 5MC's
Follow us, the 5 MCs
本気の フライデーナイト
Our Friday night in full swing
make it? break it?
Brand new generation
感じるままアガれ アガれ
Get hyped as you feel it, get hyped
華麗に降臨 only, only one
Gracefully descending, the only, only one
退屈な Neverland
A boring Neverland
速攻で抜け出せ I say
Break out immediately, I say
Ready or not?
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
朝まで make some noise
Make some noise till morning
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Stay true to myself, wild and bold
夢に強引 going, going on!
Forcing our way to our dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜いて行け
Blast straight through the middle
Can't get enough
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it? break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
What's up!
せーの！
Ready, set!
FLOW GLOW です！
We are FLOW GLOW!
皆さん、私たちのステージ見てくれてありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching our stage!
まずは私たちの自己紹介からさせてください！
First, please let us introduce ourselves!
まずは私から！
First up is me!
私がおかえりな、おかえりな、おかえりな〜って言ったら、みんなでただいま、れんごう〜って言ってほしいです！
When I say "Okaeri-na, okaeri-na, okaeri-na~", I want everyone to respond with "Tadaima, Rengo~"!
そして挨拶の最後のぶらぶら〜もせーのって言うので、よかったら一緒に言ってください！いいですか〜？
And for the "Bura-bura~" at the end of the greeting, I'll say "Ready, set", so please say it with me! Are you ready~?
ありがとー！いきます！
Thank you~! Here I go!
おかえりな、おかえりな、おかえりな〜！
Okaeri-na, okaeri-na, okaeri-na~!
ありがとう！おかえり！私の元においで！リオナ・イン・ザ・ハウス！
Thank you! Welcome home! Come to me! Riona in the house!
FLOW GLOWのリーダー、響咲リオナです！せーの！
I'm the leader of FLOW GLOW, Isaki Riona! Ready, set!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you~!
めっちゃ嬉しい〜！
I'm so happy~!
本当に今ここでみんなと会えたことすごく幸せです！
I'm really so happy to be able to meet everyone here right now!
そしてFLOW GLOWのみんなとここでステージをね、この日を迎えられたことをとても幸せに思います！
And I feel so happy that we could welcome this day on stage together with all of FLOW GLOW!
今日は一日楽しんでいってくださーい！
Please enjoy yourselves all day today!
続いて〜！
Next up~!
はーい！
Yeees!
ニコたん！行くぞ！
Niko-tan! Let's go!
ニコたんが〜、せーの、きた〜！
Niko-tan has... Ready, set, come~!
ホロライブ DEV_IS FLOW GLOW のお笑い担当、虎金妃笑虎でした！ニコたんないよ〜！
I'm Koganei Niko, in charge of comedy for hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOW! Niko-tan nai yo~!
あー、嬉しー
Ah, I'm so happy.
ニコたんもコール＆レスポンスってやつやっていい？
Can I do one of those call-and-response things too?
もちろんだよ！
Of course!
「ニコたんはー」って言ったら、トラだと思う人は「トラ」、人だと思う人は「人」って言ってください！
When I say "Nikotan is...", if you think I'm a tiger, say "Tiger!", and if a person, say "Person!"
え、どっちでもいいよ！
Wait, either is fine!
オッケー、分かったー！ニコたんはー？
Okay, got it! Nikotan is...?
人ー！
A person!
お前らとは今日が最後のステージ...
Today is my last stage with you guys...
やだー！壊さないでー！
No! Don't ruin it!
はい！すーが「水主はー？すーの充電」って言ったら、「足りてるー！」って言ってください！
When Su says "For Su-pis, Su's charge is...?", please shout "Is enough!"
水主はー、すーの充電？
For Su-pis, Su's charge is...?
足りてるー！
Is enough!
わー！ありがとうー！FLOW GLOWのエロい宣伝担当、水宮すーでーす！
Yay! Thank you! I'm Su Mizumiya, FLOW GLOW's sexy promo rep!
偉いね。うわ、今日もでっかいです。次、ヴィヴィ！
Good girl. Wow, it's huge today too. Next, Vivi!
おらー！
Hey!
ごめっ！ごめんごめん！
Sorry! Sorry, sorry!
え、どっち？
Wait, which way?
本当にごめん！
I'm really sorry!
「エンジン全開ー！」って言ったら、「レッツゴー！」って言ってください！いきますよー！
When I say "Engine full throttle!", please say "Let's go!". Here we go!
エンジン全開ー！
Engine full throttle!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
キャー！ありがとうー！FLOW GLOWのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千夜佳でーす！
Yay! Thank you! I'm Chiyaka Rindo, DJ and driver of FLOW GLOW!
そして最後に！
And finally!
はい！皆、ヴィヴィはもう分かるよな！ヴィヴィが「せーの」って言ったら、「ウ〜」で...
Yes! Everyone, you already know, right? When Vivi says "Ready, set...", with "Oooh...",
あ、まだ早い！まだ早い！やばいやばい！
Ah, too early! Too early! Oh no, oh no!
幕張でお漏らしです。
An accident here at Makuhari.
やめて！お漏らしやめて！
Stop it! Stop calling it an accident!
今のは予行練習ね、みんな！準備バッチリね！オッケー！
That was a trial run, everyone! You're all set! Okay!
皆、声出す準備出来てるかー？！
Everyone, are you ready to shout?!
せーの！ウ〜...
Ready, set! Oooh...
ヴィヴィー！
Vivi!
わー！みんなありがとうー！
Wow! Thank you, everyone!
いつもキラキラな、キラキラヴィヴィでーす！
Always sparkling, I'm Sparkly Vivi!
はい！ということでね、hololive 5th Fes. Stage 3が始まりました！2日目の夜になります！
Yes! So, hololive 5th Fes. Stage 3 has begun! It's the night of Day 2!
会いたかったよ、みんな！温まってるかー？
We missed you, everyone! Are you all warmed up?
そしてですね、今回はなんと新しい試みが...
And this time, we actually have a new attempt...
あ、でもハッシュタグがその前に！
Ah, but the hashtag before that!
じゃあハッシュタグからいきますか！
So shall we start with the hashtag then!
#ホロライブフェスEXPO26 Day2 です！
It's #hololivefesEXPO26 Day2!
熱いねー！
It's so hype!
みんなたくさんポストしてください！配信組もありがとうー！ポストしてね！
Everyone, please post a lot! Streaming viewers, thank you too! Be sure to post!
はい、じゃあ続いて...今回トロッコがね、みんなの客席に来たんじゃないですか？
Alright, next... this time, the carts came right by your seats, didn't they?
客席に！どうだったー？近くで見てくれましたか、FLOW GLOWを？
In the seating area! How was it? Did you see FLOW GLOW up close?
見たかー？ちょっと太もも近すぎた気が...
Did you? I feel like the thighs were a bit too close...
そうそう！皆さんの下から見られる太もも、ちょっと恥ずかしかったわ。
Yeah yeah! Having everyone look at my thighs from below was a bit embarrassing.
太もも最高でした！ヴィヴィのお尻もやばいから！
The thighs were awesome! Vivi's butt is amazing too!
ちょっとちょっと！まずいまずい！ほらほら、何やってんの！
Wait, wait! Bad, bad! Hey, what are you doing!
ダメだよ！俺らのステージだからやりたい放題！
No way! It's our stage so we do whatever we want!
あと何？ズルいズルい！ずるーい！
What else? That's unfair, unfair! So unfair!
やめましょうね、元に戻りましょう！
Let me stop you there, let's head back to our positions!
言うことあるんじゃないの？
Don't we have something to say?
ということで、YouTubeやTikTokでご覧の方は、なんとここまでとなってしま...
So, for those watching on YouTube or TikTok, unfortunately this is where it ends...
いやー！嫌だー！
Nooo! Don't go!
こんな感じでね、なっている方はですね、ぜひ概要欄から配信チケット買えますのでね、ぜひよろしくお願いいたします！
For those of you watching like this, you can buy stream tickets from the description, so please check it out!
だってこの後5人で合体するところも見れないわけでしょ？
Because otherwise you won't get to see the 5 of us combine later, right?
やらないやらない！やらないからね！
We won't, we won't! We're not doing that!
ということでね、ここまでということで最後に私達も合体する...
So yeah, since this is the free preview end, lastly we'll also combine...
会場の皆さんとね、合体していきたいと思いますけど...
We'd like to combine with everyone in the venue...
みんなと？！みんなと合体していきたい...
With everyone?! We want to combine with everyone...
ひとつになろうね！ということで、なんと私達からお願いがあります！
Let's become one! So, we actually have a request for you all!
私達ここ5分割ぐらいかな？目の前のメンバーにペンライトの色を変えてもらうことって出来たりしますか？
We're divided into about 5 sections here, right? Could you change your penlight colors to match the member right in front of you?
おねがいしまーす！
Thank you!
ライト、ライト綺麗！
Look, the penlights are so pretty!
ピンク、ピンク！ 綺麗じゃない？
Pink, pink! Isn't it so pretty?
すごーい！
Wow, amazing!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
綺麗だねー！
It's so beautiful!
ね、やっぱり私たちもフェスに出れたということで
You know, since we got to perform at the fest too...
先輩たちがいつもやってるウェーブやりたいよね！
We want to do the wave our seniors always do!
やりたい！ やりたい！
We want to! We want to!
じゃあ私から「うにょ〜ん」って行くから...
Okay, so I'll start with a "Unyon~"...
下がればいい？ 上がればいい？
Should we crouch down? Stand up?
そうじゃない！ 違う！ 違う！ 怖い怖い！
Not like that! No, no! Scary, scary!
間違えた！ 走るんで、あの...
I messed up! I'll run, so...
そうだね、私たちがいるところを「ういー」ってやってもらえると...
Right, if you could raise your lights as we run past...
ま、みんな慣れてるよね！
Well, everyone's used to it, right!
オッケー！ じゃああっちから...
Okay! Then from over there...
ゆっくり始めよう！
Let's start slowly!
あっちに向かって走ろうよ！
Let's run towards that side!
オッケー！ わかった！
Okay! Got it!
あっちから...
Starting from there...
Chloeの色からですよ！
From Chloe's color!
Chloeの色からか！
Oh, starting from Chloe's color!
行きますよ！ はい、せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set...
う〜〜〜！
Wooo〜!
あ、来たー！
Ah, here it comes!
すごーい！
Amazing!
綺麗ー！
So pretty!
すごーい！
Awesome!
イエーイ！
Yay!
すごーい！
Incredible!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
はい、じゃあ戻るよ
Okay, let's head back to our spots.
はい、ということで幸せな時間をありがとうございましたー！
Well then, thank you so much for this wonderful time!
いやぁ...
Man...
じゃあ最後の決めゼリフ、行きますか！
Now, shall we do our final catchphrase?
行きますか！
Let's do it!
じゃあみんな、魂込めて...
Everyone, put your heart and soul into it...
今日の思いを全て込めて言いましょう！
Let's say it with all of today's feelings!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ライディン・オン・ドリームズ！
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
The free portion has ended! Thank you for watching!